Who are you?
你到底是誰
I've already said it just now...
剛才我已經說明過了…
Let me change my question.
我換個問題
You saw my true form, didn't you?
你…看到我的真面目了吧
I'M THE VILLAINESS, SO I'M TAMING THE FINAL BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
THE VILLAINESS PULLS OUT ALL THE STOPS
(反派大小姐輪番上陣)
Answer me if you don't want to die.
若不想死就回答我
Are you keeping quiet?
保持沉默嗎
Yet you are saying you want to help me?
這樣還敢說要協助我
What do you want to do to me?
你想對我做什麼
Fine. I'll explain.
那我就開始說明吧
Come out, Ribbon.
緞帶 出來
Ask it to stop licking.
快叫牠別舔了
I want to protect you.
我想保護你
Protect me?
保護…我…
As you can see, I can summon demons.
如你所見 我能呼喚魔物
I'm not working with the church that wants to hunt you at least.
至少跟正在追尋你的教會 不相容勢力
My target is Ashtart.
我的目的是阿斯塔蒂
You know about Ashtart, right?
會長也知道阿斯塔蒂吧
Ashtart is my name?
阿斯塔蒂是我的名字
I am a half-demon.
我是半魔
The students of the academy
學園裡的學生們
and even the members of the student council don't know about this.
甚至是學生會成員都不知道這件事
My father gave me the demon name, Ashtart.
這是父親幫我取的魔物之名 "阿斯塔蒂"
It was a name I abandoned.
是不久前被我捨棄的名字
Was this a scenario in the game?
遊戲裡有這樣的設定嗎
Why did the Ashtart who announced the attack use that name?
那麼 發出襲擊預告的阿斯塔蒂 為何用這個名字
I wonder. Perhaps he wanted to make me the culprit.
誰知道 可能想把我塑造成犯人吧
Send this demon back.
讓這隻魔物回去吧
It'll be troublesome if someone sees it.
萬一被別人看到就麻煩大了
Don't approach me carelessly.
你也別隨便靠近我
I'm not one of your own.
我不是你們的同伴
President James, you are similar to the person I love.
賽姆斯會長跟我喜歡的人好像
What?
什麼
Anyway, I'll do my best to protect you.
總之 我會努力保護你
Please help me out.
也請會長協助我
Don't report it to the principal.
別跟學園長報告
I refuse.
我拒絕
Come out, Ribbon.
出來吧 緞帶
All right. Stop using demons as your shield.
好啦 別把魔物當擋箭牌
That's so despicable.
太卑鄙了
What about the demons in the town?
那麼 出現在市區的魔物呢
All of them have retreated.
都讓牠們撤退了
Good.
那就好
I want all demons that have been instigated by Ashtart to leave the town.
希望盡量讓被阿斯塔蒂煽動的魔物 遠離市區
I'll go and have a look with Belzebuth tomorrow.
明天我也跟佩魯賽博特 去附近看看
It's better if you stayed here, Master Claude.
庫洛德大人別離開這裡比較好
I understand.
我知道
However, it's uncomfortable to be so restrained.
但過得太不自由真的很不舒服
I wished...
我也想…
Are you thinking of going to the school festival?
您該不會想去學園祭玩玩吧
I think I can make friends there.
因為我覺得能交到朋友
Despite my appearance, I've never made a friend.
別看我這樣 我從未交到一位朋友
If that's your wish, I'll help you.
魔王期望的話 我就協助您吧
That's right. You should start by learning how to greet people.
沒錯 先從打招呼開始學起…
Hold on! You are here as the principal!
慢著 庫洛德大人是以學園長的身份 來到這裡的喔
I know that...
我知道…
Do you think being the Demon King is boring?
您覺得當魔王很無趣嗎
I just want to make friends.
我只是想交朋友
Keith, since he said that,
吉斯 魔王都這麼說了
let's prepare some friends immediately.
立刻準備朋友過來
You can't prepare friends.
朋友是無法立刻準備的
That's right. Aileen is familiar with socialising.
對了 愛琳對社交界很熟悉
I'll ask her to give me some advice.
請她給我一點建議吧
With her around, I won't have to give up on being human.
只要有她在 我就不用放棄更像人類
It's the academy! This is not socialising!
就說了 不是社交界 是學園
The purpose is totally different!
立場完全不一樣
You can make friends in the future.
想交朋友以後再交
But...
可是…
I won't forgive you
工作時不工作卻跑去玩
if you go and have fun when you're supposed to be working.
我可是不會放任不管的
DAY 1 OF THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL
(學園祭第一天)
We are the guard unit!
警備隊
We are going to confiscate any prohibited items.
我們要沒收違反校規物品
It's the school festival so just let it go for once.
學園祭時睜一隻眼閉一隻眼吧
Hand it over.
快點交出來
It's not the Demon Snuff.
不是魔香
Let's find the next target, Jame...
沒收後去找下個目標 賽姆…
Blue.
小藍
Why do I have to dress up like this?
為什麼我要打扮成這樣
Master Claude is concerned about the duck.
庫洛德大人很在意鴨子
I have no choice but to increase the number of ducks.
所以我只能讓鴨子的數量增加啊
Red! Blue!
小紅 小藍
Augu... Pink!
奧古… 粉紅
Can you make it?
來得及嗎
Don't you have to sign up for the contest?
你還要報名參加競賽吧
It's that late already?
已經到這麼晚了嗎
I have to go.
我得走了
What is your name?
請問您的名字
There are even outsiders participating.
也有好多社團以外的成員報名
Will Auguste win?
奧古斯特 贏得了嗎
That muscle-head should have no problem.
那個肌肉笨蛋 應該沒什麼問題
What a relief. They are still accepting entries?
太好了 報名還沒結束
The Demon King?
魔王
Master Claude?
庫洛德大人
The number of ducks has increased.
鴨子變多了
Thanks for waiting.
讓你們久等了
Principal?
學園長
I'm not the principal.
我不是學園長
Then... Demon King?
那…魔王大人
I'm wearing the Demon King's outfit
我打扮成魔王的模樣
but I'm not the Demon King.
但我不是魔王
I'm just a wandering traveller.
我只是路過的旅人
Just like a guard pretending to be a normal person?
就像警衛喬裝成普通人
I see. I'll just have to tell Keith that.
原來如此 只要跟吉斯這麼說就行了
We'll go with that.
那就這樣吧
Are you sure that's what you want?
確定要這種打扮
He's enjoying the school festival no matter how I see it.
我怎麼看都覺得 他都很享受學園祭吧
Oh. I want you to teach me how to participate in the swordsmanship contest.
對了 我想請你們教我 如何申請劍術大賽
I've completed my registration. Let me teach you.
我申請完了 教你吧
I also know some delicious food stalls.
另外 我還知道很好吃的攤位喔
Signing up is more important. There's not much time left.
申請優先吧 沒時間了
Has he always been worshipped easily
這傢伙該不會是經常被供奉的人
regardless of gender and age?
而且不分男女老少
He is staring at me.
他在看 拼命盯著我看
Are you the duck who came to get my seal previously?
你是… 之前來拜託我簽名的鴨子
I wonder why I'm very curious about you.
怎麼回事 我真的很在意你
A duck got pinned to the wall.
鴨子被壁咚
What an incredible visual.
太奢侈的立繪了
Why are you escaping?
你為什麼要逃
Well, the entry will close soon.
那個…報名要結束囉
Oh, right.
對喔
It's not bad to see Master Claude enjoying a human's life.
庫洛德大人 享受人類的生活也不錯
It would be better if I could walk with him.
如果 能跟他走在一起就更好了
Red! Bad news!
小紅 不好了
The church seems like they are trying to get rid of the demons in the academy no matter what.
教會似乎不管三七二十一 就是要解決潛伏在學校裡的魔物
They are planning to sneak Demon Snuff into the arena to expose the demons.
他們打算在競技場中混入魔香 揭露魔物的真面目
I heard they've done something to the lanterns at the venue's four corners.
聽說他們在比賽會場四角 四架燈籠做了手腳
The smell will cover the whole area once the lanterns are lit.
一點燃 味道就會擴散全場
However, if we retreated in an obvious manner,
可是 我們撤掉的方法太明顯
the church will see us as traitors and start to hunt us down.
就會被教會視為背叛者而追殺
The principal is participating in the swordsmanship contest.
學園長 要參加劍術大賽
If the Demon Snuff awakens demons
如果魔香讓魔物覺醒
and causes the principal to turn into an evil dragon...
害學園長變成巨大的惡龍…
Not just the academy,
不只是學園
but the whole empire will be in danger.
連整個國家都會有危險
We need to get Master Claude to withdraw from the contest soon.
盡快讓庫洛德大人退出劍術大賽
The Demon King cleared the preliminaries without using magic and his dominant hand.
魔王大人 不用魔法只靠左手 就打贏預賽了
It should be easy for him to lose when he has given himself such a big handicap.
他都讓步這麼多 應該很容易輸吧
My Master Claude will not lose that easily.
我的庫洛德大人怎麼可能輸
Think about it carefully.
給我認真思考
Stop flaunting your relationship.
放什麼閃
I do have a way.
方法有是有啦
Really?
真的嗎
A sleeping potion developed by Ruck.
這是琉克研發的安眠藥
It's very effective even on Demon Kings and dragons.
不管是魔王還是龍 都效果奇佳
Drugging him, right?
下藥迷昏他對吧
This is excellent water drawn from a nearby well.
這是附近井裡打上來的水 很好喝喔
Please, have a drink.
請用
I would love some.
請務必讓我嚐嚐
Do your best in the finals.
決戰 請加油喔
Thank you.
謝謝
Perhaps I'll rest for a bit.
稍微…休息一下好了
If Master Claude is asleep,
庫洛德大人繼續睡下去
he won't turn into a demon. James won't turn into the final boss as well.
他就不會變成魔物 賽姆斯也不會變成最終大魔王了
The Duchy of Mirchetta will be saved.
米爾契塔公國得救
The Bad Ending will stay away from me!
BE就會離我遠到不行
Master Claude!
庫洛德大人
It's time.
時間到了
Serena. I'm not Claude right now.
塞蕾娜 我現在不是庫洛德
I'm just an ordinary person, Claw.
只是普通人 庫洛
What is this scenario?
這是什麼設定
The potion didn't work?
奇怪 藥沒效嗎
Excuse me. Did you eat my cookie?
請問 您吃過我做的餅乾了嗎
I did.
吃了
How do you feel?
那麼…感覺如何
That girl...
那個女的…
Did she use an aphrodisiac
難道她加了媚藥
that affected the sleeping potion?
而對安眠藥造成影響
It's not bad.
還不錯
Is that so?
這樣啊…
In that case, I'll have to pull out all the stops.
既然如此 那我就要不擇手段了
KYLE ELFORD CV CHIAKI KOBAYASHI
(凱魯 艾路霍德) (CV 小林千晃)
ONE OF THE CHARACTERS THAT CAN BE TAMED IN REGALIA OF SAINTS, DEMONS AND MAIDENS 2
(聖與魔與少女的雷加利亞2) (裡攻略角色其中之一)
SIMILAR TO WALT, HE PLAYS AN IMPORTANT PART IN FIGHTING AGAINST THE DEMON.
(與沃魯特相同) (擔任跟魔物作戰的重要任務)
GOOD AT FIGHTING. HE DEFEATED A FEW PEOPLE IN THE MARTIAL ARTS CLASS.
(武藝高超 在體術課時) (曾同時打敗過好幾個人)
Auguste from year one
誰打進了決賽
will proceed to the finals!
是一年級的奧古斯特
The Demon King will be fighting as well, right?
魔王大人也會出賽吧
Who will win?
誰會贏呢
It's definitely the Demon King.
當然是魔王啊
Duck, it's you again?
又是你這隻鴨子
What do you want this time?
這次又想幹嘛
YOUR FIANCEE IS NOT A DECENT WOMAN
你的未婚妻不是什麼好女人
SHE GOT ENGAGED TO TWO BROTHERS
前後跟兄弟兩人訂婚
HOW UNSEEMLY
輕浮女
PRINCE CEDRIC ABANDONED HER
被塞多利克王子拋棄的…
BECAUSE SHE WAS TRASH
廢物女人
It has begun!
開始了
Demon King...
魔王大人…
And a duck?
跟鴨子
I thought you were just a weird duck
我原以為你只是隻奇怪的鴨子
but turns out you are quite something.
但看來不是省油的燈
I overdid it.
我做過頭了
I just wanted to anger him a bit.
本來只是想讓他稍微不悅而已…
You humiliated my fiancee.
你侮辱了我的未婚妻
An apology is not enough to save you!
別以為道歉就能了事
You don't have much strength.
力道好輕…
I don't know if you are a man or a woman.
也不知道你是男是女
Who are you?
你究竟是何人
Whatever.
算了 不用說了
I just need to destroy your costume!
只要斬碎玩偶衣就好了
That's it.
就是這樣
I'll just get Master Claude to destroy the lanterns.
讓庫洛德大人破壞燈籠
Red!
小紅
Are you all right?
你沒事吧
What's going on?
怎麼回事
Is this a performance before the final match?
這是比賽前的餘興節目嗎
That's interesting!
好有趣
Three against one.
三比一
The ducks are acting weirdly.
鴨子的謎樣行為
Aili. The people from the church are trying to light the lantern.
艾里 教會的人要點火了
Where are you looking at?
看哪呢
What is your purpose?
你的目的是什麼
Did you humiliate Aileen purposely?
你是故意侮辱愛琳的嗎
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事
Auguste! Help us out!
奧古斯特 快來幫忙
How?
幫什麼忙
Say something like the Demon King's fiancee is ugly!
快說 魔王的未婚妻是醜女之類的
You can't simply say that even if it's the truth!
這種真心話不能說出口吧
This is bad.
糟糕
I did it.
成功了
However...
可是…
Are you all right?
沒事吧
What's going on with this commotion?
這場騷動是怎麼回事
A performance before the final match.
決賽前的餘興節目
It's to show everyone the strength of the guard unit.
目的是讓大家看到警備隊的實力
Principal, we are very sorry.
學園長 真是抱歉
Was it also a show to call my fiancee ugly?
說我的未婚妻是醜女 也是餘興節目嗎
Especially that red one.
尤其是紅色的那隻
He humiliated my fiancee.
他侮辱了我的未婚妻
I won't be satisfied until I cut him down.
不砍了他我不罷休
Besides, shouldn't you apologise
而且道歉的時候
by showing your real face?
不是應該以真面目視人嗎
You are right.
說得也是
Not good. This is terrible.
糟糕 情況不妙啊
What are you doing, my foolish master?
笨蛋主人你在幹什麼
Keith, have you returned?
吉斯 你回來了嗎
That's right.
沒錯
I flew over as soon as I heard someone was having fun here.
我得知某人正在玩耍 所以就如敘述般地飛了過來
Sire, we have returned after we carried out your orders.
魔王 我們已完成您的吩咐 因此回來了
What is this mess?
這個慘狀是怎麼回事
I'm sure it's your fault!
絕對是你搞出來的吧
I'm the one who broke them but I didn't do it on purpose.
的確是我弄壞的 但非我本意
Do you think that excuse will work?
您以為這種藉口行得通嗎
Don't be angry. I prepared souvenirs.
別這麼生氣 我準備了土產
The church members who are lying there.
就是倒在那邊的教會人員
They seemed to have done something to the lanterns.
他們似乎在燈籠裡動了手腳
Take it back and investigate it.
拿回去仔細調查
Did he notice the Demon Snuff?
難道他注意到魔香了嗎
When?
什麼時候開始注意的
My master has troubled all of you.
我家主人 給大家添麻煩了
I will keep a close eye on him so he doesn't appear at the school festival anymore.
我會緊盯著他 不讓他再出現在學園祭裡
Then, the final...
那麼 決賽…
You win.
你贏了
I lost to you with my left hand.
我的左手輸給你
So, you are the champion.
所以 你是冠軍
I am the champion?
我是冠軍
Let's fight again next time.
找一天我們再好好比一場吧
As a friend.
以…朋友的身份…
Of course.
那當然
-Magic? -It's my first time seeing it.
-魔法 -我第一次看到
Amazing!
好厲害
I'll leave the rest to you.
接下來就拜託你們了
I'll be looking forward to seeing your real face next time.
至於你的真面目 就期待下次吧
Hence, the first day of the school festival ended in peace.
就這樣 學園祭第一天平安結束了
Although the church has left the academy,
雖然教會退出了學園
we still don't know the true identity of Ashtart
但還是不清楚 阿斯塔蒂的真面目
"DAY 2 OF THE SCHOOL FESTIVAL" and the source of Demon Snuff.
(學園祭第二天) 和魔香的出處
The prize for winning the title of Princess Lily White is Demon Snuff?
白百合公主的獎品是魔香
That's right. Jasper said an anonymous letter has been sent to the empire's news outlet.
對 加斯帕說匿名信寄到了 皇都的新聞社
Aili's secret organisation has people in the newspaper as well?
艾里所屬的祕密組織 在報社裡也有人脈
That's amazing.
好厲害
The ball comes after the swordsmanship contest?
劍術大賽結束後是舞會
We need to confirm the prize as soon as possible...
得趕快確認獎品…
We can't do that due to the security detail.
有人戒備 所以無法確認
After all, the ball is in the parents' council's jurisdiction.
畢竟舞會是家長會的管轄
What should we do then?
那麼該怎麼辦才好
Excuse me,
請問
can I participate in the contest?
能否讓我參加比賽
We can get the prize if I become Princess Lily White.
只要我被選為百合公主 就能得到獎品
That's it!
就是這招
Will you be fine?
妳沒問題嗎
Don't pass out once you're on the stage.
不會一站在舞台上就昏倒
I can do it.
我…沒問題
Everyone knows that Rachel is Serena's rival
大家都知道蕾切爾 是塞蕾娜的競爭對手
so it should be fine.
所以應該沒問題
It should work.
應該可以吧
I have no objections.
我沒有異議
Me too.
我也是
It'll have to do.
那麼 就這樣吧
I'll be preparing my dress.
好的 我立刻去準備禮服…
I sold my dress.
禮服…被我賣掉了
Don't worry. You can still make it.
放心吧 時間上還來得及
Pick one with Isaac.
妳跟艾札克去選一套吧
Why me?
為什麼是我
I'll be depending on you.
交給你了
Fine. Let's go.
好吧 走囉
Rachel.
蕾切爾
Please wait!
請等我一下
I didn't expect Demon Snuff to be the prize for Princess Lily White.
沒想到白百合公主的獎品是魔香
I don't remember this scenario in the game.
我記得遊戲裡沒有這個劇情啊
Sorry. Thanks for waiting.
不好意思 久等了
Isaac told me this is just right.
艾札克說 這樣不會太過華麗剛剛好
It suits you a lot.
非常適合妳
I will do my best.
我會加油的
I might not look it, but I'm good at etiquette and social skills.
別看我這樣 其實我的禮儀儀態 和社交技巧都很不錯
I'll change Isaac's opinion about me.
我會讓艾札克刮目相看的
If you become Princess Lily White,
如果被選為白百合公主
will you choose Isaac as your partner?
妳會選擇艾札克當妳的舞伴嗎
Why him?
為什麼是艾札克
When I wanted to break off my engagement,
當我說出要解除婚約時
my parents objected and my fiance was very angry.
我雙親反對 對方也非常生氣
Many people blamed me so I wondered if I had made the right choice.
在眾多責備下 我很煩惱自己的選擇是否正確
Isaac told me something.
艾札克對我說了一句話
You did well.
做得好
I felt very proud then.
那時 我為自己感到驕傲
So, I'll also do my best this time.
所以這次我也會加油的
I won't lose to Serena.
絕不會輸給塞蕾娜
It felt the same as when I attended the ball.
跟我當時參加晚會的心情一樣
Rachel.
蕾切爾
Are you planning to enter the Princess Lily White contest?
妳打算參加白百合公主選美嗎
Yes. I changed my mind.
是的 我改變主意了
Is that so? Let's both do our best.
這樣啊 彼此加油囉
That is such a nice dress.
這套禮服真漂亮
Show me.
讓我看看
Rachel!
蕾切爾
I'm fine...
我沒…
Oh no, my dress!
討厭 我的禮服
Miss Serena fell down the stairs?
塞蕾娜小姐摔下樓梯了
Her dress is ruined.
禮服破了
The contest will begin soon.
快要比賽了耶
Did she do it on purpose?
該不會是故意的吧
All of you...
妳們幾個
Master Aili.
艾里大人
Rachel.
蕾切爾
Rachel, don't worry about it.
蕾切爾 妳別介意喔
That was just an accident.
這只是個意外
I'll try to do something about the dress.
禮服我會想辦法的
This woman...
這個女的…
How dare she bully my cute junior.
竟敢欺負…我可愛的學妹
Let's have a fair contest.
我們正大光明的比賽吧
What happened?
發生什麼事了
Are you all right?
沒事吧
I'm fine...
我沒事…
How can you dance when you can't even stand?
妳都站不穩了 這樣怎麼跳舞
No way. I'll be fine.
怎麼這樣 我沒問題的
Just give up on becoming Princess Lily White.
放棄選白百合公主吧
But...
可是…
Rachel, can you lend me the dress?
蕾切爾 這套洋裝能借我嗎
Is he serious?
他是認真的嗎
Aili is so brave.
艾里真有勇氣
It might suit him surprisingly well.
搞不好意外地適合他
No way.
不會吧
Good evening, gentlemen.
各位紳士好